socialserve.com 2016-10-11

# Socialserve.com - Privacy Guidelines

Socialserve.com takes our users' and clients' privacy seriously. As a nonprofit social service agency, we believe in the individual's right to confidentiality and privacy. Strict measures are taken to ensure the highest levels of user and client confidentiality. As new services are added to our site, each one is designed to the highest levels of industry-standard security appropriate for the service type. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy guidelines. 

**What this Privacy Guideline Covers**

  * This Privacy Guideline covers Socialserve.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that Socialserve.com collects when you are on the Socialserve.com site, and when you use Socialserve.com's services. This guideline also covers Socialserve.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Socialserve.com's partners share with Socialserve.com or that Socialserve.com may collect on a partner's site. 
  * This guideline does not apply to the practices of companies that Socialserve.com does not own or control, or to people that Socialserve.com does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

  * Although the majority of our site is anonymous for users, Socialserve.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Socialserve.com account, when you use certain Socialserve.com products or services [clearly stated when applicable], when you visit certain Socialserve.com pages, and when you subscribe to certain services and/or newsletters. Socialserve.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our partners. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * Socialserve.com will not sell, rent, loan or give your personally identifiable information to anyone for any reason unless: 
    * We have your consent to share the information; 
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Socialserve.com to provide a product or service to you; 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal processes; or 
    * We find that your actions on our Websites violate any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Session Cookies**

  * Socialserve.com sets and accesses security control cookies known as "Session Cookies" on your computer. Session Cookies maintain your region and pertinent security information during your site usage. _Any cookie set by Socialserve.com will expire and/or will be deleted from your computer upon exiting your browser or if your session is inactive for a period of time._

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

  * Socialserve.com gives you the ability to edit your Socialserve.com Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want Socialserve.com to contact you about updates and new services by contacting us. 
  * You may request deletion of your Socialserve.com account by contacting us and requesting that your account be deleted. 

**Security**

  * Your Socialserve.com Account Information is encrypted and password-protected for your privacy and security. 
  * In certain areas Socialserve.com uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

**Changes to this Privacy Guidelines**

  * Socialserve.com may amend this guideline from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we collect or use personal information, notification will be posted in this section. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us. 

Copyright © 2016 - [Emphasys Software](http://emphasyshfa.com/) - All rights reserved  
Email: info@socialserve.com - Socialserve.com - PO Box 35305 - Charlotte, NC 28235 

Phone: 704.334.8722 - Fax: 704.334.0779   
Toll-Free: 1.877.428.8844 \- Toll-Free Fax: 1.866.265.7811 \- TDD/TTY: 7-1-1 [ [ Relay Service](https://www.fcc.gov/encyclopedia/telecommunications-relay-services-directory) ]   
Page Loaded: 10/10/16 20:45 (Eastern Time) - Version 4.0
